COREY SADER

Prior Lake, MN | (715) 441-6972 | corey.sader@gmail.com | Portfolio: www.coreysader.com

SUMMARY

To obtain a challenging and rewarding position in the computer industry which will utilize and expand my HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and jQuery skills as a Web Developer.

PROFILE

Highly qualified and technically skilled professional offering over fifteen years of progressive experience in the workforce. Able to use strong communication skills and a team-oriented approach in working with people at all levels of the organization.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

LANGUAGES

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- jQuery

- PHP
- MySQL
- SASS
- LESS
- C#

SOFTWARE/FRAMEWORK

- Visual Studio
 ASP.NET
- Android Studio
 XCode
- Illustrator

- Sublime
 Notepad++
 Photoshop CS5
 3D Max
- VR Toolbox

- Vray
- Photovista
 AutoCad 2008
- Revit
- Premier

EXPERIENCE

April 2015 – Aug 2015

TempWorks Software - Eagan, MN

Web Developer Intern

- QA Testing, fixed bugs and examined software for additional bugs
- Helped create step by step Instruction Manual for their applicant tracking software
- Agile work environment

Jan. 2008 – June 2011

Preferred Interactive LLC - Savage, MN

Owner/Manager/Creative Director (design department)

- Created startup company with 2 other partners
- Developed website and application design
- Created and streamlined all feature processes
- Create tutorials for all design department processes
- Trained contractors on all design department processes
- Managed up to 30 contract employees
- Delegated application and texture creation projects
- Managed Quality Assurance and Quality Control
- Collaborated on future planning and goal setting
- Responsible for accounts payable for contract employees
- Other general administrative duties as needed

COREY SADER

Prior Lake, MN | (715) 441-6972 | corey.sader@gmail.com | Portfolio: www.coreysader.com

April 04 – May 10 (FTE) May 10 – Jan. 13 (Consult.)

Toltz King Duval Anderson (TKDA) – Fridley, MN

Technician (specializing in 2D/3D architecture visualization)

- Helped in the recording and reviewing of shop drawings
- Created drawings for clients according to client information, specification and as per the good industry practices
- Produced and updated detailed drawings and solid models using sketches, models, layouts, notes
- Obtained reviews and approvals from architects of project leads
- Worked solely creating 2D/3D photo realistic computer renderings/animations to win a project, to help sell an idea to investors, for fundraising, or simply to visually communicate a concept (main role)

April 2003 - April 2004

Durda Design/Drafting - Fridley, MN

Steel Fabrication Drafter

- Drafted steel fabrication shop drawings
- Worked in a small office setting with little to no direction

March 1999 - July 2001

Dynamic Digital Design Inc. - Minneapolis, MN

2D/3D Architectural Modeler/Animator

- Designed accurate 2D/3D models in AutoCad and 3D Studio Max
- Created 3D architectural models and animations for use in video demonstrations, interactive virtual reality walk through, fundraising and also for training purposes
- Co-Designed architectural environments for custom 3D training simulators, using a custom built 3D engine. Gave the client the ability to visually communicate their information into a photo realistic image of their concept before it is built.

EDUCATION

Minnesota School of Business

Richfield, MN

Bachelor of Science: Software Development

Graduated: September 2016

GPA: 4.0

Hennepin Technical College

Brooklyn Park, MN

Associates in Arch. Drafting and Design

Graduated: May 2004

Academy Education Center

Bloomington, MN

Certificate in Computer Art and Animation

Graduated: 1998

Northern State University

Aberdeen S.D.

Major: Computer Science (1993-1997)

VOLUNTEER WORK